Guide to the Records of the Women's Philharmonic M1470
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series XXIV: Restricted Files
  This file contains personal financial information such as bank account numbers, credit card numbers or resumes with attached interviewer comments.
  - 1997-1998 Major Gifts (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - 1997-1998 Subscriptions and financial information (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Renditions Music Services donation (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - 2001 Donor subscriptions (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - 1999 Donor Solicitation Reports (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Staff Salary and Bonus structures (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Marketing Director Job announcement/description (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Marketing/Development (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Donations Records 2003 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Symposium registration forms (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Gala 2000 ticket orders (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - City Box Office Ticket orders (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Merchandise orders filled, 1996 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Merchandise orders filled, 1995 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Merchandise receipts, 1999 (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Merchandise: credit card slips (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Major Donor Checks, 2000-2003 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Donors: 2001-2002, season cancellation notes (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Merchandise orders pulled, 1998 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - Individual major donors (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - Donor contacts (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Major Donor's Checks received, 1998-1999 (Box 175, Folder 1)
- Series XXV: Nan Washburn
  Nan Washburn
  This file contains concert, organizational planning and women composer research materials of Nan Washburn, co-founder, Artistic Director and Associate conductor of the Women's Philharmonic. These materials include programing lists, orchestra seating diagrams, orchestra personnel rosters, correspondences with composers, guest artists and guest conductors. Also included are personal correspondences between Ms. Washburn, colleagues and conference attendees.
  - Nan Washburn correspondence and repertoire solicitations/inquiries, 1983-1986 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Nan Washburn correspondence and repertoire inquiries, 1984-1986 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Nan Washburn correspondence and NWCRC (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - American Music Center correspondence (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Female Composers research and miscellaneous music programs from 1988 (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - Wild Goose Duck Fishing retreat: women in music (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - 1984-1985 Orchestra planning and materials (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - 1985 String Quartet Performance materials (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - 1985 Season notes and correspondence (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - November 1985 Concert and Joann Falletta correspondence (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - December 1985 Children's concert and planning materials (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - 1985 Nan Washburn memo and production notes (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - 1986-1987 Season programming notes and correspondence (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - 1986-1987 season materials and auditions (Box 162, Folder 9)
  - 1987-1988 Season materials (Box 162, Folder 10)
  - February 1986 Baroque concert and correspondence (Box 162, Folder 11)
  - May 1986 Concert materials (Box 162, Folder 12)
  - October 1986 Boulanger concert notes (Box 162, Folder 13)
  - November Sacramento Tour materials, 1986 (Box 162, Folder 14)
  - 1987 Proposed Woodwind Quintet Tour and materials (Box 162, Folder 15)
  - April 1987 concert with Mary Watkins materials (Box 162, Folder 16)
  - Children's concert materials, 1987 (Box 162, Folder 17)
  - February 1987 concert with chorus notes and correspondence (Box 162, Folder 18)
  - 1987-1988 Season planning; budgets, timelines, schedules (Box 162, Folder 19)
  - Children's concert, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - February 1988 concert (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - March 1988 Chamber music (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - April concert, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - October 22, 1988 concert (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - November concert, 1987 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - 1988 Benefit program with Lily Tomlin (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - February 11, 1989 concert (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - March 11, 1989 concert (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - May 5, 1989 Baroque concert (Box 163, Folder 10)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League concert materials, June 1989 (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - Children's concert, 1989 (Box 163, Folder 12)
  - Children's concert, 1989-1990 (Box 163, Folder 13)
  - October, 1989 (Box 163, Folder 14)
  - February, 1990 (Box 163, Folder 15)
  - March, 1990 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - April, 1990 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Recording Session materials, May 1989 (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Reading session, 6/1990 (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - Misc. artist correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - Article sketches, research ideas, programming stats (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - American Music Center Library suppliments (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - Assorted articles on women and music (Box 164, Folder 8)
  - Asian Women composers (Box 164, Folder 9)
  - Misc. resources for program notes (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Library correspondence (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Concert Programs, 1982-1985 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Program notes and bios (Box 165, Folder 3)
- Series XXVI: Media/Ephemera
  - Audiocassettes/VHS tapes (Box 170)
  - Computer Media (diskettes/hard-drives) (Box 171)
  - Sweatshirts/T-shirts (Flat-box 174)
  - Oversize posters (Map-folder 1)
  - Oversize posters (Map-folder 2)
  - Oversize posters (Map-folder 3)